hexamob.com 2016-01-12

# Privacy policy - Hexamob

Hexamob, SL (hereinafter Hexamob), with CIF B12929881, owner of the website “hexamob.com” (hereinafter WEBSITE) and mobile applications (hereafter, APPs) in which download process has brought you to this electronic document ensures full compliance with the obligations under the Law 15/1999 of December 13, Protection of Personal Data (LOPD), Royal Decree 1720/2007 of 21 December , by approving the Regulations implementing the Act and other regulations in the field, setting the policy as one of the cornerstones in the action lines of Hexamob. 

Hexamob informs the user of the existence of a file of personal data exclusively for Hexamob and under his responsibility, created with data obtained through WEB or, where appropriate, by the statements from your mobile device during use of APPs, for the purposes of managing the relationship with Hexamob users, the provision of services and products offered in THE WEB, or APPs, as well as carrying out promotional and advertising activities by any means, including sending communications electronic (email, SMS, MMS, WHATSAPP, LINE, TELEGRAM, or by any other electronic means of similar characteristics that emerge in the future) that may be of interest to the user, adapting our offers to your preferences and needs. This file has been duly registered in the General Data Protection Register. 

Hexamob engages in the processing of the data included in the file mentioned above, to respect its confidentiality and use in accordance with the stated purpose of the file, and to comply with all the technical and organizational measures to prevent the loss, or unauthorized access, in accordance with the provisions of the Regulations implementing the Act, approved by Royal Decree 1720/2007 of 21 December. 

The user expressly accepts the inclusion of data collected while browsing the web, using APPs, or provided by filling in any form, including those provided through any means during established business relationship, in the mixed file of personal data identified in the previous section. During data collection, the user will be informed in the form of mandatory or voluntary nature of the requested contribution itself. However, the data collected while browsing through Google Analytics tool, such as the terminal from which the user connects automatically recorded and may be associated with other information provided by users who have used our forms, upon acceptance of the privacy policy and legal notice THE WEB. During the download process or use of APPs will apply not make, model and operating system version of your mobile device, information associated with your email account. This information may be used to direct offers to Hexamob votes USER or personalized based on the information that has been collected Hexamob thereof. The user can disable or delete cookies installed on your computer by following the steps in our Cookie Policy. 

Hexamob informs the user that to ensure full availability of the data in your files has concluded its hosting services and maintenance of data with different suppliers located in the European Union as well as in USA. These suppliers have signed a contract to provide services Hexamob, and found inside the European Economic Area or U.S. entities are adhering to the principles of “Safe Harbor” (safe harbor), in accordance with Decision 2000/520/EC . the Commission on July 26, 2000 For more information about the Safe Harbor program, visit: <http://export.gov/safeharbor>

The USER agrees unequivocally international communication and data transfer in terms of expressing finishes. This transfer will take place automatically upon submit your information to Hexamob, so if you are not agree with it must provide them to refrain from it. The user can exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation or opposition, and where applicable, withdrawal of consent to receive information, by writing to the address of your permanent establishment located in Monestir de Poblet,13 1 B, 12540 – Villarreal (Castellon – Spain), or if you prefer, send your request from the email address you have provided when registering at THE WEB TO privacy@hexamob.com. 

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept [Read More](http://hexamob.com/es/aviso-legal-y-politica-de-privacidad/#cookies)
